[
    {
        "id": 724,
        "question": "How to list all Kubernetes services in the current namespace?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "kubectl get-all services",
            "answer_b": "kubectl print services",
            "answer_c": "kubectl dump services",
            "answer_d": "kubectl get services",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Kubernetes"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Linux",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_d"
    },
    {
        "id": 913,
        "question": "Which of the following are core Kubernetes objects?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Pods, Services, Volumes",
            "answer_b": "Pods, Docker, Volumes",
            "answer_c": "Pods, Services, Droplets",
            "answer_d": "None of the mentioned",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Kubernetes"
            }
        ],
        "category": "DevOps",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    },
    {
        "id": 930,
        "question": "How can a company deal with a monolithic codebase issue?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "By transitioning from a monolithic codebase to a microservice design so that different microservices can be classified as containers.",
            "answer_b": "By building a large Docker image containing the monolithic codebase and deploying it as a single container to Kubernetes",
            "answer_c": null,
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Kubernetes"
            }
        ],
        "category": "DevOps",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    },
    {
        "id": 1000,
        "question": "Kubernetes can be configured in a multi-Master Node configuration. True or False?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "True",
            "answer_b": "False",
            "answer_c": null,
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Kubernetes"
            }
        ],
        "category": "DevOps",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 705,
        "question": "Deployment Controllers are part of",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Master Controller Manager",
            "answer_b": "kube-scheduler",
            "answer_c": "etcd manager",
            "answer_d": "API Controller Manager",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "correct_answer": "answer_a",
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Kubernetes"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Linux",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    }, {
        "id": 1016,
        "question": "Which of the following are Kubernetes Objects?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Kubernetes objects are Pod, Service and Volume.",
            "answer_b": "Kubernetes objects are  Host, Auth and Cluster.",
            "answer_c": null,
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Kubernetes"
            }
        ],
        "category": "DevOps",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 723,
        "question": "Which command is used to create resources in Kubernetes?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "kubectl create -f ./my-manifest.yaml",
            "answer_b": "kubectl deploy -f ./my-manifest.yaml",
            "answer_c": "kubectl apply -f ./my-manifest.yaml",
            "answer_d": "kubectl fuse -f ./my-manifest.yaml",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Kubernetes"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Linux",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_c"
    }, {
        "id": 715,
        "question": "What language was Kubernetes written in?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Go",
            "answer_b": "C++",
            "answer_c": "Java",
            "answer_d": "C",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Kubernetes"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Linux",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 956,
        "question": "How to remove two pods labelled 'production' and 'development'",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "$ kubectl delete pods -l 'env in (production, development)'",
            "answer_b": "$ kubectl trim pods -l 'env in (production, development)'",
            "answer_c": null,
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Kubernetes"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Docker",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 718,
        "question": "Which command is used to create a Kubernetes service?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "kubectl set service",
            "answer_b": "kubectl create service",
            "answer_c": "kubectl deploy service",
            "answer_d": "kubectl expose",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Kubernetes"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Linux",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_d"
    }
]
